

Atahan Koç

Computer Engineer

Contact me:

Cep: 05426912608

E-posta: koccata@gmail.com

Linkedin:

https://bit.ly/37TcCSZ

Adres: İstanbul / Türkiye

Github:

https://github.com/AtahanKocc

Dribbble:

https://dribbble.com/AtahanKoc

Personal Profile

I am a graduate of Computer Engineering from Istanbul Medipol University. I am a person who likes to learn and improve himself. I have had the opportunity to experience many technologies so far. Outside of software, I like watching movies and playing video games.

Educational Background

Istanbul Medipol University

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

September 2017- October 2022 Activities and Communities: IEEE | GDSC Medipol Uni.

Projects made during the university;

- Bookstore Application Data Structures
- Mini Bank Management System C
- University Website Project Web programming
- Blood Donation System Databases
- Student Clubs Application Software Fng.
- Classifieds App Application For Mobile Devices (Flutter)
- Emotion Recognition For AI Assisted Student Counseling (Engineering Project)

Anadolu University

Business management and administration

2019-2023

Experiences

Software Engineer Geovision Group January 2023 - Present

Software Engineer Intern Technix Technology June 2022 - August 2022

Freelance Software Engineer Fiverr & Upwork March 2022 - August 2022

Software Engineer Intern Nabi Bilgi Teknolojileri September 2020 - October 2020

Professional Skills

BackEnd

C#, ASP.NET MVC, ASP.NET, LINQ, Entity Framework

Front End

TypeScript, JavaScript, React

Databases:

Relational Database (SQL, PostgreSQL) / Non-Relational Database (MongoDB)

Certificates

2021 - Introduction to Machine Learning | Global AI Hub

2021 - Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning | Google DSC Medipol University

2021 - Mobile Development | Google DSC Medipol University

2021 - Web Development | Google DSC Medipol University

2021 - Blockchain | Google DSC Medipol University

2019 - Microsoft Yazılım Uzmanlığı Kursu| Smartpro eğitim akademisi

References

Bülent Nahırcı Software Specialist Geovision Group 05448151999